photaki.com 2014-02-13

# Image Bank - Stock Photos

Photaki as the operator of the personal data provided via this website is committed to respecting your privacy. In this sense, Photaki drafted this policy on the processing of your personal information to let you know of the information collected online and the use made of it.

In this Privacy Statement we inform you about our policies and practices in this regard, as well as on the options available to you in connection with how your data are obtained on the Internet and how that information is used.

This website is subject to Spanish law. In case of any dispute arisen as a result of using this website, the Spanish courts shall have exclusive jurisdiction.

http://www.photaki.com is owned by GRAPHIC RESOURCES SL, with registered office at C / Fernan Nunez, Office No. 4, Malaga, Company tax code number B93183366.

By using this site, you indicate that you understand and agree to the terms and conditions herein.

### I Collection of Personal Information

**a)  Personal data collected automatically**

When you visit our web site, some information may be collected automatically, such as the website where you obtained our address, your IP address, information about your browser, and access times to our site. We also collect information concerning your browsing on our site as the pages you visited or the activities you performed. We may combine the information about your visit with the personal information you provide us.

**b)  Personal data provided by you**

When you sign up as a user of the site, you must complete a registration form and provide personal information such as your name, ID or CIF, mailing address, telephone number, fax number, email address, name of your company, your ID and password. Some additional information will also be collected to carry out the procurement of licenses for use of images or to provide some products or services (e.g. credit card number and billing address). Algunas informaciones adicionales serán también recopiladas para llevar a cabo la contratación de licencias de uso de imágenes o poder proporcionarle algunos productos o servicios (ej: el número de tarjeta de crédito y la dirección de facturación).

### II Use of personal data

The personal information collected by Photaki is for internal use and for the following specific purposes:

 -To process orders and issue invoices.

 -For the maintenance and updating of your account.

 -To send you our products, promotions and marketing communications.

 -To keep you informed of our new products and services.

 -To establish a profile of activity of our site.

 -To optimize your use of Photaki.com.

Photaki can also use some of the information of the user accounts for studies of solvency.

### III Conservation of personal data

The personal data referred to in Section I, will be kept for as long as necessary to carry out the purposes for which they have been collected.

### IV Sharing of your personal data

By providing your personal data to Photaki.com, you agree that:

-They can be handled with, stored or transferred (either free or paid) by any affiliate, branch or joint venture by Photaki.com

-Photaki.com can share your personal information with service providers acting on their own, content providers, financial intermediaries to the transaction, or home delivery services for the purposes specified in section II above. These companies will solely and only obtain the necessary information to carry out the service hired and will not be allowed to use it for any other purpose. Moreover, these companies are obliged to keep the data provided confidentially.

 -This information may be disclosed in the context of a merger, acquisition, or sale of the assets of the company and in case of insolvency and liquidation of the company involving a transfer of personal data as part of assets of the company.

 -these data may be disclosed by law if Photaki.com, acting in good faith believes that such action is necessary in legal proceedings for the resolution of a claim or for the protection and safeguarding rights of society.

Except for what is stated by this policy for handling personal data, Photaki.com does not share personal information regarding the users of the site with third parties.

### V Exercise of rights regarding the processing of personal data

You can at any time, revise, correct or modify your personal details by accessing the section "My Account" on our website. If you prefer, you can also send your request for amendment at [info@photaki.com ](mailto:info@photaki.com) email.

To delete your personal information from our files, you can exercise this right by sending us your request in writing to the following email address:: [info@photaki.com](mailto:info@photaki.com). 

### VI Use of cookies

Cuando visita el sitio web de Photaki.es, éste envía a su ordenador una “cookie”. When you visit the website Photaki.es, it sends your computer a "cookie". A "cookie" is a small file that resides on the hard drive of your computer and contains electronic identification information which identifies the user's computer (this is not personal information). Cookies allow Photaki.es improve the functionality of your website to make it more useful by storing information about your preferences. For example, "cookies" to identify the result of previous image searches. You have the option of preventing the creation of "cookies" by selecting the appropriate option in your browser. However, if you choose to decline "cookies" you may not be able to benefit from all features of the website.

### VII Security

Protecting your personal information is paramount to Photaki.es. In order to protect the confidentiality of your personal data, Photaki.es has a number of protection mechanisms. For example, when you enter sensitive information (such as your credit card data), the information provided by you is encrypted by using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). SSL encrypts the data transferred between the user and the server, rendering it in a format that is unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information. However, be aware that there is no “perfect security” on the Internet. Therefore, we cannot guarantee that Photaki.es is impenetrable or invulnerable to hacking.

### VIII Links

Please note that this website may contain links to other sites which have their own privacy policies. Photaki.es not responsible for the practices of these sites and we encourage our users to carefully read the privacy statements of each web site that collects personal identifiable information.

### IX Information relating to minors

We have no intention to solicit or collect personal information from children under 18. If you are under 18 do not provide any information on this site.

### X Changes

Photaki.es reserves the right to modify its policy concerning the processing of personal data at any time, and according to their criteria, or because of changes in legislation, jurisprudence or business practice. Such modifications will be posted on this website indicating the top of this section the date of last update.

If you have any questions about our policy for handling personal data please contact us by calling (+34) 665 810 196 or send an e-mail at [info@photaki.com](mailto:info@photaki.com).
